Ok, all righty
We are really excited about this new version of Firefox
and I'd like to show you why.
Hi, my name is Jonathan Nightingale, I'm the Vice President of Firefox here at Mozilla
This is our biggest update in a while and you are gonna see it right away
but the changes go more than skin deep
There are a lot of improvements under the hood, that I'd like to talk to you about as well
The new Firefox menu combines all of the command functions that you're gonna need from Firefox into a single place
and gets out of your way when you don't need it.
You can even create bookmarks with a single click and manage them from the same place.
The redesign of Firefox tabs makes it more beautiful, yes, but also means that the tabs you are not looking at disappear into the background
so they don't act at some much of a distraction
With the new Firefox menu in customization mode, it's easier than ever to make Firefox your own
You can remove buttons you don't use, you can reorganize things to make it more natural to you
Not just in the toolbar, but in the menu as well
and if there's functions that you need quick access too, you can bring them up
if you print a lot of documents for example, put it on the toolbar so you don't have to go hunting in menus
This also works with the thousand of Firefox add-ons out there.
If you want the "Send a Kindle" add-on or a Pinterest add-on as part of your menu
you can drag and drop it, just like any other part of Firefox
Part of making Firefox your own also means being able to take it with you
That's why we've made it so easy to set-up Firefox Sync
You can nick your bookmarks, history, passwords
you can access them from any device just by creating an account
and let Firefox take care of the rest.
And as with all things that we do, your information will be kept secure
Mozilla is a mission-driven organization, dedicated to promote openness, innovation and opportunity on the Web
That's why we build Firefox around the idea of protecting your privacy
and that's why we are the most trusted company on the Internet
We are really excited about the new release of Firefox and we built it for you
So give it a try, and thanks for watching.